{"data":[{"question":"This comic book ___ before long.","a":"will be published","b":"will be publishing","c":"will have been published","d":"is published","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Before long= soon \n- Simple future tense + passive voice","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"___ that the earth was the center of the universe.","a":"People were once believed","b":"People were said","c":"People were believing","d":"It was once believed","answer":"4","explain":"\n- It is believed (that): to think that something is true or possible, although you are not completely sure\n- Simple past tense: used to describe past facts or generalizations which are no longer true. ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"Did you telephone the governor's assistant? \"Yes, he ___ back before tomorrow evening.\"","a":"is expected","b":"expects","c":"is to expects","d":"expected","answer":"1","explain":"\n-\u00a0 Simple Present to talk about scheduled events in the near future. This is most commonly done when talking about public transportation, but it can be used with other scheduled events as well)+ passive voice","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"An exhibition of sculptures ___ at the gallery next month.","a":"is to be held","b":"are to be held","c":"will hold","d":"are holding","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Simple present tense (use Simple Present to talk about scheduled events in the near future. This is most commonly done when talking about public transportation, but it can be used with other scheduled events as well)+ passive voice \n- Subject (an exhibition)- singular noun","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"___ that Wendy and Vincent can pass the oral test this time.","a":"It is hoped","b":"That is hoped","c":"It hopes","d":"That hopes","answer":"1","explain":"\n- \" It\" is a dummy subject: we use \"it\" as a subject when we don't want to show who is the true subject \n- It's said\/believed that= people say\/believe that","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"Nobody ___ to smoke inside the house.","a":"allow","b":"allows","c":"are allowed","d":"is allowed","answer":"4","explain":"\n-  Simple present tense (Use the Simple Present to express the idea that an action is repeated or usual. The action can be a habit, a hobby, a daily event, a scheduled event or something that often happens)+ passive voice\n- Subject (Nobody)-> singular noun\n","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"It is said that the university ___ 100 years ago.","a":"was built up","b":"has set up","c":"was set up","d":"had been set up","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Simple past tense (Use the Simple Past to express the idea that an action started and finished at a specific time in the past) + passive voice \n- Set up: to start a company, organization, committee etc [= establish]","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"These books ___ for parents.","a":"wrote","b":"write","c":"are writing","d":"are written","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Simple present tense: used to talk about sth in general \n- Passive voice","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"Kent asked his father for some money, but he ___ a good scolding.","a":"was given","b":"gave","c":"was being given","d":"had been given","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Simple past tense (same tense with verb \"ask\") + passive voice","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"Why does Henry look so unhappy? \"He has ___ by his friends.\"","a":"laughed at","b":"laughed","c":"been laughed at","d":"been laughed","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Present perfect tense + passive voice\n- Laugh at somebody\/something: to make unkind or funny remarks about someone, because they have done or said something you think is stupid","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"}]}